http://www.hcfcu4u.org/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
View Document in PDF Format >
Health Care Family Credit Union is owned by its members and run by a board of directors you elect. You can be confident that your financial privacy is a top priority of this credit union. We are required by law to give you this privacy notice to explain how we collect, use and safeguard your personal financial information. If you have any questions, please contact a member service representative at HCFCU.
We are committed to providing you with competitive products and services to meet your financial needs, which necessitates that we share information about you to complete your transactions and to provide you with certain financial opportunities. In order to do so, we have entered into agreements with other companies that provide additional financial products for you to consider or services to us.
Under these arrangements we may disclose all of the information we collect, as described here, to companies that perform marketing or other services on our behalf to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements. To protect our members’ privacy, we only work with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of information we provide. We do not permit these companies to sell to other third parties the information we provide to them.
What Does Health Care Family Credit Union Do With Your Personal Information
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Information we receive from you on membership and loan applications and other forms
Information about your transaction with us or others
Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency
Information obtained when verifying the information you provide on an application or other form, such as from your current or past employers or from other institutions where you conduct financial transactions
When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Health Care Family Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Health Care Family Credit Union share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes — such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes — to offer our products and services to you
Yes
Yes
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
Yes
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes — information about your transactions and experiences
No
We do not share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness
No
We do not share
For non affiliates to market to you
Yes
Yes
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
HEALTH CARE FAMILY CREDIT UNION
What we do
How does Health Care Family Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.
How does Health Care Family Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account or pay your bills
Apply for a loan or show your government-issued ID
Show your driver's license
From Credit Bureaus, Affiliates or other Companies
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State Laws and Individual Companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing (See below for more on your rights under state law)
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Health Care Family Credit Union has no Affiliates
Non-affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Non-affiliates we share with can include organizations such as insurance companies or service providers who provide products available to you because of your membership at Health Care Family Credit Union
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners can include organizations such as credit card companies or service providers
Other important information
Missouri state law does not have a specific Privacy Law Disclosure Requirement
Find A Location
Main Office
2114 S. Big Bend Blvd.Richmond Heights, MO 63117(314) 645-5851
St. Peter’s OFFICE
4599 Executive Centre Pkwy.St. Peters, MO 63376(636) 449-3305
Shared Branches > Free ATMS >
×
*IMPORTANT UPDATE: Virtual Branch & Bill Pay Upgrades* Read More >
Search Health Care Family Credit Union
×
Secure Login Center
Online Banking
E-Statements
Credit Card Access
Log In
Enroll Now
Demo
Pay Your Loan Online
Perform a Financial Checkup Today!
Stay on top of your finances with our financial checkup. Fill out the form and find out how much you could save today!
Learn More >
×
Do you want to pay with your Health Care Family Credit Union account?
Login
Continue To EZCARD
Transferring from your Health Care Family Credit Union will not charge you a fee.
×
First Name
Last Name
Phone Number
Email Address
Comments
Current month ye@r (4 digits) day *
Leave this field empty *
×
Certificate of Deposit InquiryPlease contact us regarding a CD with Health Care Family Credit Union.
First Name
Last Name
Phone Number
Email Address
Comments
Current month ye@r (4 digits) day *
Leave this field empty *
×
IRA InquiryPlease contact us regarding an IRA with Health Care Family Credit Union.
First Name
Last Name
Phone Number
Email Address
Comments
Current month ye@r (4 digits) day *
Leave this field empty *
×
Home Mortgage InquiryPlease contact us regarding a home mortgage with Health Care Family Credit Union.
First Name
Last Name
Phone Number
Email Address
Comments
Current month ye@r (4 digits) day *
Leave this field empty *
×
Money Market Investment Account InquiryPlease contact us regarding a Money Market Investment Account with Health Care Family Credit Union.
First Name
Last Name
Phone Number
Email Address
Comments
Current month ye@r (4 digits) day *
Leave this field empty *
×
You are now leaving Health Care Family Credit Union’s website.
You are now leaving Health Care Family Credit Union’s website to visit a site operated by a third party. Please be aware that Health Care Family Credit Union does not provide and is not responsible for the content, security, privacy policies, downloads or any other product or service on any external third-party site.
Cancel
Continue
×
